#### **CAREER PROFILE**

I am a qualified Diagnostic Radiographer with an ambition to aid in improving health care, patient care and making the patients' health care experience a positive one. I am an honest, reliable, responsible and hardworking individual and I hope to make a difference in the healthcare field. References available upon request

### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Community Service Diagnostic Radiographer**

Manguzi Hospital

- I learnt how to operate dark room equipment.
- I learnt a sufficient amount of isiZulu to be able to communicate effectively with my patients.
- I learnt how to work independently due to 'on-call' and after-hour shifts being worked alone

# **Student Diagnostic Radiographer**

January 2015 - present

Jan. 2019 - Dec. 2019

CPUT

Thesis (2018): CT vs MRI in diagnosing glioblastomas of the brain

## Student Diagnostic Radiographer

January 2015 - present

Various Hospitals

- Hospitals include: Groote Schuur Hospital, Victoria Hospital, Red-cross Children's Hospital, Somerset Hospital, Retreat Day Hospital, Bishop Lavis Day Hospital
- Interacted with patients, developing patient care and inter-personal skills as well as an empathetic outlook towards health care
- Computer and technology literacy, while working with the medical machinery and computers
- I successfully completed a course in information literacy and was awarded distinction. (Apr. 2015)
- Worked in a team environment, learning the value of teamwork and also working independently
- While at university I learnt various skills including:
  - o time management through completion of assignments
  - o leadership qualities through being appointed leader in multiple group projects
  - o organizational qualities through planning and delegating tasks

# **EXTRAMURAL**

#### Au Pair

I have been babysitting for 10 years. From this I have learnt how to handle responsibilities and expectations placed upon me.

### Soccer and netball

I have been playing team sports for a number of years and it has taught me social skills and how to be a team player, attributes I hope to utilise in my work environment.



**(**+27) 71 869 8618

### **EDUCATION**

BSc (Hons) Diagnostic Radiography - Cum Laude Cape Peninsula University of Technology, Jan. 2015 - Dec 2018

#### LANGUAGES

English (native

#### INTERESTS

Hiking / Trail-running

Soccer and netball

Animals

Travelling